partypeeps2000.com 2011-06-03

# Privacy Statement

PartyPeeps2000.com is dedicated to providing visitors with a highly interactive and personalized experience, while at the same time protecting users from any unexpected use of personally identifiable information (your name, e-mail address, telephone number).  
Like other Web publishers, we collect information from users in order to deliver more individualized content and advertising to them, but we do so only within the guidelines in this policy.

 **HOW WE GATHER INFORMATION FROM USERS**  
PartyPeeps2000.com gathers information you provide to us when you register for access to certain portions of our site.  
We also gather information you provide to us when you participate in interactive areas of our site, including sweepstakes and contests, voting and polling activities and message boards.  
Some of the demographic information we request will be identified as "optional" during the registration process.   
You may change or update your registration information at any time at the 'Edit Registration' section.

 **WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**  
The information you share with us may be used in several ways.  
Typically, during your visit to our sites, we will use your registration and demographic information to deliver targeted editorial content.  
We will use personally identifiable information to communicate with you about: 

  * your registration and customization preferences; our privacy policies; 
  * services and products offered by PartyPeeps2000.com and other affiliated companies; 
  * and other important information. We may also communicate with you about changes and improvements to PartyPeeps2000.com and about sweepstakes or promotions we are conducting. 

Personal information collected by PartyPeeps2000.com may also be used for other purposes as determined by PartyPeeps2000.com. For example, to inform users of offline events or special promotions available to PartyPeeps2000.com members only. Also, from time to time we or our advertising and promotional partners may call to your attention products, special offers and unique content we believe might be of interest to you.  
However, if you prefer not to receive direct communications from our advertisers, you will be given an opportunity to decline by (not) using the “stay updated” box.  
Personal information collected by PartyPeeps2000.com may also be used for site administration and troubleshooting, contest entries and other matters you initiate.

 **NOTE**  
You should be aware that if you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g., user name, e-mail address, or other messages) in forums or in the commentboxes of PartyPeeps2000.com, that information can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties.  
Such activities are beyond the control of PartyPeeps2000.com.

 **AFFILIATED AND LINKED SITES**  
PartyPeeps2000.com expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users.  
Be aware, however, that our promotional partners, advertisers, sponsors, third-party Internet sites, and content providers accessible through our site may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices.  
During your visit to our site you may link to (or view as part of a frame that includes PartyPeeps2000.com content) certain content that is actually created by a third party.  
PartyPeeps2000.com is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.  
Users should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing personally identifiable information through co-branded, affiliated, framed or linked sites.

 **POLICY CHANGES**  
The foregoing policy is effective as of October 1, 2001.  
PartyPeeps2000.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.  
This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

  * NEWS
    * News
    * Search
    * Archive
    * Submit
    *  
    * Interviews
    * Search
  * EVENTS
    * Events Agenda
    * Events Submit
    *  
    * Locations
    * Search
    *  
    * Promotors
    * Booking Offices
  * MEDIA
    * Pictures
    * Picture Charts
    * Search
    *  
    * PP2G.TV Videos
  * FUN
    * Releases
    * Search
    * Archive
    * Submit
    *  
    * Artists
    * Labels
    *  
    * Contests
  * MEMBERS
    * Search
    * Lucky Shot
    * New Members
    * Last Logged In Members
    * Birthdays
    * Deluxe Members
    * Rankings
    *  
    * Forum
    * Active Topics
    * Search
    *  
    * Polls
    * Search
    *  
  * SHOP
    *  
    * Hotgear Shop
  * INFO
    * About Us
    * Partners
    *  
    * Contact
    *  
    * Privacy Statement
    * Terms Of Service
    *  
    * Faq

PP2G © 2000-2011 v3.2.192
